To prepare your Windows devices to auto enrolled in Microsoft Intune, we need to
configure the MDM users scope. So without the MDM users scope, the device will not
be able to automatically enroll in Intune if you've configured the right
TPO. So what you need to do is to go to Azure Active Directory admin center and
here we need to click Azure Active Directory and then we need to scroll down and
then here we have the option called Mobility MDM and MDM. So click on that and
you can see we have one option Microsoft Intune. So click on it. And right now
you can say is that the MDM users scope is set to none. You can't only set to
some which of course you're going to select a specific group for what is set
everything to all. You can see I'm our advisor not to modify any of these
because I'm going to find this you may receive error during the auto enrollment and
for the MDM we should just leave this other moment go and I'm going to find
when I'm going to be doing the MDM in this training. So let's just leave this for
now and then here we need to just click Save. So now it has been configured. I'm
ready to go to the topic of our auto enrollment.